styledesigncollege.com 2015-04-07

# Style Design College

'SDC', 'we', 'us ', 'our' means SDC Online a brand & trademark owned by Style Design College. **'ECD'** refers to the associated company based in Milan, Italy. 'you' means the individual using the Website or SDC learner or applicant.

'Course Materials' means the materials provided that enable you to complete a SDC Online Course.

'Course' means the online or offline Course Materials, which are in a format that allows (i) downloading the Course Materials via the Website or (ii) accessing and viewing the Course Materials online (or a combination of both (i) and (ii)). 

'Course Fee' means the fee payable for a SDC Course.

'Agent' means a third party organisation that has a contract with us to promote the products and services on the Website. 

### PART A - TERMS APPLYING TO ALL USERS OF THE WEBSITE

Please read these Terms of Use ('Terms') carefully before using the Website.

Additional terms and conditions apply if you register as a user of the Website (Part B) and if you buy, or access courses that are sold from the Website (Part C). 

Ownership of Rights 

SDC is the owner of this Website and the SDC Online trademark and brand. We reserve the right to withdraw all or part of the Website at any time. By using this Website you agree to be bound by these Terms, the Privacy Statement (Part D) and the Copyright Statement (Part E).

Your Responsibilities

You acknowledge that you are responsible for making back-up copies of all your data and taking appropriate precautions against viruses, hacking and other types of computer misuse. 

Damage to your Computer

While we try to ensure that the Website does not contain any error, defect, malfunction or corruption, we do not accept responsibility for any damage to or loss of data on your computer system, network or server that results from the download or use of the Website or any materials made available via the Website (except for death or personal injury caused by our negligence). 

Accessibility of the Website

Although we use reasonable endeavours to ensure that the Website is available 24 hours a day 7 days a week, we cannot promise that access to the Website will be uninterrupted or error free. There may be occasions when access to the Website is interrupted for emergency maintenance or repairs, or to carry out upgrades to improve the performance or functionality of the Website. Access may also be interrupted due to failures of telecommunications links and equipment, which are beyond our control. You accept that you will not have a claim for breach of contract (either against ECD, SDC Online, SDC Corporation or an Agent or Reseller of SDC courses) or otherwise in respect of such period of unavailability. You also acknowledge that we cannot be held responsible for any delay or disruptions that are inherent in the operation of the Internet and the World Wide Web, including viruses. 

Our Liability to You

We shall not be liable to you for any of the following types of loss or damage arising out of or in connection with your use of the Website or any or content and/or facilities provided via the Website: 

  * any loss of profits, loss of earnings, loss of anticipated savings, goodwill or revenue;
  * any loss or corruption of data; or 
  * any indirect or consequential loss.   

The maximum aggregate liability of SDC for all claims, whether made in contract, tort under statute or otherwise (including in each case negligence) which are not otherwise excluded under these Terms ("Claims") shall be limited to €100 in respect of one incident, or series of incidents arising from a common cause, in each 12 month period commencing from the date that you register, provided that the maximum aggregate liability of SDC for all Claims arising as a direct result of technical advice provided by us shall be subject to the monetary cap on liability set out on Part C of these terms. 

The exclusions and limitations of liability contained in this section do not apply to: 

  * any loss or damage resulting from death or personal injury caused by our negligence;
  * loss or damages arising from our fraudulent misrepresentation; or 
  * any other losses which may not be excluded or limited by law.   

Each provision of this Paragraph shall be construed separately as between you and us. If any part is held by a court to be unreasonable, inapplicable or unenforceable, then the other parts shall still apply. 

Any right to access the Course Materials is personal to you. You may not transfer your rights to access the Course Materials to another person. 

General

If any provision of these Terms becomes void or otherwise unenforceable in whole or in part, the validity of the remainder of these Terms shall not be affected. 

If either we or you fail to enforce, or delay in enforcing, any respective rights or remedies under these Terms, such failure or delay shall not operate as an agreement to waive that right or remedy, and shall not prevent us from exercising that right or remedy in the future. 

These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us and you in relation to the provision by us to you of the Website, any Course Materials (and related technical support), and they replace and supersede any prior arrangements between us and you in relation to the same. You acknowledge that you are not relying on any statement made by SDC or any of our Agents, Resellers or representatives with regard to the Course Materials and related technical support other than those expressly set out in these Terms (which include, for the avoidance of doubt, the description of the Course Materials and related technical support set out on the Website). Nothing in this paragraph shall exclude or restrict our liability for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation. 

These Terms are governed by and shall be construed in accordance with International law. Any dispute arising between us and you under or in connection with these Terms shall be subject to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the Italian courts. 

Contacting SDC

You can contact us: 

  * by email at [sdconline@eucollegeofdesign.com](mailto:sdconline@eucollegeofdesign.com)
  * by post at ECD, Via Telesio 25, Milan, 20145, Italy  

Purpose of the Website 

The purpose of the Website is to provide individuals with information on the range of courses and other products and services offered by or via the Website and to facilitate online access to these products and services where they are delivered online and by long distance/correspondence learning. 

Copyright and Use of Materials

The materials on this Website are protected by our and by copyright and other intellectual property rights as described in the SDC Online Copyright Statement (Part E). 

Where you have been granted access to Course Materials, either as a result of your own online purchase or because you have been granted access rights by someone else, you may not re-sell access to the materials or otherwise distribute "course material" to anyone else. 

Third Party Links 

The Website may provide links to third-party websites from time to time. This may include links to sites owned by associated companies of SDC, including Agents and Resellers of SDC courses. These third-party links are provided for your convenience only and are accessed at your own risk. We are not responsible in any way for the content of any third party website or for goods or services provided by the operators of such websites. 

Amendments to the Terms 

We reserve the right to amend these Terms from time to time. When we make a change we will update this page of the Website. The date of the last revision to these Terms is provided at the end of the Terms. We recommend that you revisit this page from time to time to ensure that you are aware of any changes that we have made to these Terms.

### PART B - TERMS APPLYING IF YOU REGISTER AS A USER OF THE WEBSITE

Individuals will need to register in order to purchase or access Courses that are sold from the Website. By registering, you are creating a "user account". Please read Part B carefully before registering as a user of the Website. 

Registration 

To register as a user and learner you agree that the information that you provide to us on registration and at all other times will be true, accurate, current and complete and you agree that you will ensure it is kept accurate and up to date at all times. We may refuse to accept your application to register as a user of SDC Online for any reason in our absolute discretion. 

Password 

When you register as a user of the Website you will be asked to select a user name and password. As you will be responsible for all activities that occur under your user name and password, you should take care to keep your user name and password confidential. You must notify us immediately of any unauthorised use of your user name or password or if you believe that your user name or password are no longer confidential. We reserve the right to require you to alter your username and password if we believe that they are no longer secure or for routine security. You can alter your password via the Website. 

The information that you provide to us upon registration and at any other time is subject to the SDC Privacy Statement (PART D of these Terms).

Technical Support 

SDC provides technical support to individuals who have registered on the Website. Technical support is provided on the basis that it is your responsibility to ensure that any computers that are used to access the Website and the Course Materials meet the relevant minimum specification described on the Website. 

On the Website we will provide: 

  * Technical specifications for each Course
  * Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs) to help you to diagnose / overcome any technical issues 
  * A phone number and e-mail address for our customer helpline.   

We use reasonable skill and care in providing such technical support and will use reasonable endeavours to ensure that technical support is available but cannot guarantee uninterrupted availability. 

SDC will provide the following customer support: 

  * A customer helpline. This helpline will normally be available, with core hours of 8am to 5pm GMT and will be accessible by phone and email. The helpline will be staffed by appropriately trained staff.
  * The helpline will provide customers with:   

    * Pre-purchase information and support
    * Assistance with the purchase and enrolment process
    * Post-sales technical support and help with any account management. 
    * Tutor support (e.g. content-specific) support, after arranging an appointment with the designated tutor.  

You acknowledge and accept that periods of downtime may be required in respect of the SDC IT infrastructure in the circumstances outlined in these Terms (dealing with unavailability of the Website) and that technical support may not be available during such periods of downtime. You accept that you will not have a claim for breach of contract (either against us or your SDC Agent or Reseller) or otherwise in respect of such period of unavailability. 

We exclude all other warranties, express or implied, as to the performance and availability of the technical support service, except as expressly stated in these Terms and Conditions. We do not guarantee that the technical advice provided by us will resolve your technical problems. If you decide to avail of such technical advice, you should ensure that such advice is strictly followed. 

Suspension and Termination of your Account 

You agree that we may at any time without notice terminate your user account and delete all information stored on it, unless it contains Course Materials that have not exceeded their expiry date.

### PART C - TERMS & CONDITIONS OF THOSE PURCHASING ONLINE COURSES

Detailed Description of Services

ECD / SDC / SDC Corporation are businesses in the Higher Education sector who market and sell online and long distance study courses to the general public. Courses consist of short vocational courses to certificate, diploma and degree courses requiring longer study. Course content is loaded onto each student’s online account and the student is able to receive tutoring from qualified tutors by means of online system, email, Skype or telephone. 

Formation of a Contract of Sale (if you buy online courses from SDC) 

In order to purchase and access a Course, you must register as a user of the Website (see Part B). If you are already registered as a member of SDC Online, you can log onto your customer account using the user name and password that you chose when you registered. 

When you place an order for a Course you are offering to purchase that Course on these Terms. We shall have the right to decline or cancel your order. You can change your order at any time up to the submission of your credit or debit card details by using the "back button" of your web browser. 

You will receive confirmation (via the website and by email) once payment has been approved on your card transaction. A legally binding agreement shall come into existence when you agree to the terms of use and sale before purchasing the course. 

We reserve the right to withdraw at any time Courses advertised for sale on the Website. 

Delivery Policy

Subject to availability and receipt of payment, requests will be processed within 2 days and delivery confirmed by way of access to the online system & confirmation email. 

The Course Fee for any Course at any given time will be displayed on the Website. Course Fees are quoted in Euros. The total cost of the Courses is shown on the shopping basket prior to the online transaction. 

We will debit the Course Fee from your credit card on or after the day you make an order for a Course. 

We reserve the right from time to time to change the amount of the Course Fee. In the unlikely event that due to a technical error, the amount of the Course Fee is incorrect, we will notify you as soon as we reasonably can. If the correct price is higher than advertised, you will be entitled to choose between receiving a refund of the monies that you have paid to us (in which case Course Materials will not be sent to you and/or you will not be able to access the Course Materials for the purposes of downloading or completing the Course) or to pay the balance of the Course Fee to us. If the correct price is lower than advertised, we will refund the balance of the Course Fee to you. 

Other Charges 

You may incur additional charges to your Internet Service Provider while you are accessing and / or downloading the Course Materials. Additional charges may also be payable to third parties for use of the software necessary to access and / or download the Course Materials. You are responsible for paying these charges. 

Return and Refunds Policy

The provision of services by SDC is subject to availability of courses. In cases of unavailability, SDC will refund the client in full within 30 days. 

If you have purchased online via the SDC Online website

You may cancel your purchase of Course Materials within the following periods: 

Online Course Materials: You may only cancel your purchase of Course Materials within a period of 1 working days (24 hours) beginning the hour the program was activated. 

If you have purchased online from one of our Authorised Resellers:

You may not cancel your purchase of Course Materials if purchased from a reseller unless the reseller permits you to do so in which case the resellers refund policies will come into effect.

 ** _If payment was made through PayPal and you received an official PayPal invoice for your purchase:_**

If payment is completed using PayPal, after receiving a PayPal invoice from the Institute - you may cancel your program and receive a full refund of funds paid within a 48 hour period from activation. 

Exceptions to the right to cancel:

You cannot cancel your purchase of Course Materials if you have accessed the Course Materials (as the contract will be deemed to have commenced at the time of access), unless the Course Materials are faulty. 

Exchange and Transfer Policy

You may only exchange the course you have selected and purchased for a different course and may only transfer to a different course without payment if these changes are made within 3 days (72 hours) of commencing the course. 

If the learner changes their course within the 72 hours of commencement they are expected to pay any difference in course cost. If the new course selection is of a lower cost no refund will be deemed owing by SDC.

Any learner transferring to a different course after 3 days (72 hours) from commencement is required to complete any outstanding payments of their current course and will be required to pay the cost of the new course without refund or discount. For this reason SDC strongly recommends that the learner makes the correct choice in course.

Your Right to Use the Course Materials and your Related Obligations 

SDC Course Materials: In consideration of receipt by us of the Course Fee, we grant to you a non-exclusive, non-transferable licence to use the Course Materials for the sole purpose of personal home or work use. As such, you may not make copies of the Course Materials, you may print for your personal use so many pages of the Course Materials on the Website as are reasonable for private purposes. 

Save as expressly set out in these Terms, you may not modify, copy, reproduce, re-publish, upload, post, transmit or distribute in any way any of the Course Materials. Any use of the Course Materials not expressly permitted in these Terms is strictly prohibited and will constitute an infringement of either our copyright or our other intellectual property rights, and / or the copyright or other intellectual property rights of our licensors. 

Customer Privacy Policy 

SDC/ECDSDC Corporation shall take all reasonable steps to protect the personal information of users. For the purpose of this clause, "personal information" shall be defined as detailed in the Promotion of Access to Information Act 2 of 2000 (PAIA). The PAIA may be downloaded from: <http://www.polity.org.za/attachment.php?aa_id=3569>

Payment Options Accepted

Payment may be made via Visa, MasterCard, Diners or American Express credit cards or by bank transfer into the Style Design College bank account, the details of which will be provided on request.

Credit Card Acquiring and Security

Payments by Pay Pal will be made to SDC. Credit card transactions will be acquired for SDC via PayGate (Pty) Ltd who are the approved payment gateway for Standard Bank of South Africa. PayGate uses the strictest form of encryption, namely Secure Socket Layer 3 (SSL3) and no credit card details are stored on the website. Users may go to www.paygate.co.za to view their security certificate and security policy.

Customer Details Separate from Card Details

Customer details will be stored by SDC separately from card details which are entered by the client on PayGate’s secure site. For more detail on PayGate refer to www.paygate.co.za

Merchant Outlet Country and Transaction Currency

If choosing to pay by credit card method and not Pay Pal - the merchant outlet country at the time of presenting payment options to the cardholder is South Africa. Courses are sold in Euros (€) with the Transaction being converted into the currency of South African Rand (ZAR). 

Responsibility

SDC takes responsibility for all aspects relating to the transaction including sale of services sold on this website, customer service and support, dispute resolution and delivery of goods. 

Quality of the Services 

SDC will provide the Course Materials in accordance with the Course description which is set out on the Website. 

We do not make any commitment to you that the Course will meet any specific requirements that you have and we expect you to take reasonable care to verify that the Course in question will meet your needs. We do not make any commitment to you that you will obtain any particular result from your use of the Course Materials or that you will obtain any particular qualification on completion of the Course (unless otherwise stated on the Website).   
SDC does not make any commitment that the Course Materials will be compatible with or operate with your software or hardware. ECD/SDC/SDC Corporation are private International education providers and therefore do not guarantee any accreditations for any of its offered programs and courses but act within their legal right and registration to offer under-graduate programs on an International level.

All representations, warranties and/or terms and/or commitments not expressly set out in these Terms (whether implied by law, conduct, statute or otherwise) are hereby excluded to the maximum extent permissible at law. 

Our Rights to Stop Providing the Services to You 

If you have purchased online Course Materials via the SDC website, we will make the Course Materials available to you for the maximum period permitted for completion of each course after which point we will suspend your access to the course. This period starts immediately following the issue of your confirmation email. If you purchased the materials from one of our Resellers the access period is from the date the Reseller gives you access to the materials. If you wish to access the Course Materials after your access has been terminated, you will need to submit a new order via the Website or contact the Reseller from whom you purchased the Materials. In certain circumstances, for example if you suffer from a disability, we may extend the time period in which you may access the Course Materials. To enquire about such an extension, please contact us via the details at the end of Paragraph 1. 

We reserve the right to suspend your access to online Course Materials immediately in the event that: 

  * you fail to comply with Paragraph of our Terms which deals with the manner in which you are permitted to use the Course Materials and the Website; or 

  * you fail to conduct yourself in an appropriate manner when communicating with or receiving support from us. By this we mean that you act in such a way as to threaten, intimidate or otherwise harass our staff.

If we exercise this right, we will notify you and will then immediately suspend your access to the Course Materials. 

Our Liability to You

We make every effort to perform our obligations under our contract with you. However, we cannot be held responsible for delays or failure to perform if such delay or failure is caused by circumstances beyond our reasonable control. In the event of a delay, we will perform our obligations as soon as reasonably possible. 

We are not responsible to you for any data that you lose either (a) as a result of accessing the Course Materials; or (b) during completion of any Course via the Website. It is your responsibility to ensure that you regularly save and back up (i) all data which you hold on the computer from which you are accessing the Course Materials, and (ii) all data that you are inputting when completing the Course. 

In the event that we recommend that you either enable cookies or download certain publicly accessible software to ensure that your computer is capable of accessing the Course Materials, you do so at your own risk. 

Except as set out in these Terms, our maximum aggregate liability to you for any claim that you may have against us, under or in connection with, the provision by us, to you, of the Course Materials and associated technical support which is not otherwise excluded in these Terms (including without limitation where such claim arises as a direct result of any negligent technical advice provided by us) shall be limited to the amount of the Course Fee which has been paid, or is payable, by you or on your behalf. 

Each provision of this paragraph shall be construed separately as between you and us. If any part is held by a court to be unreasonable, inapplicable or unenforceable, then the other parts shall still apply. 

Country of Domicile

This website is governed by International law and SDC chooses as its domicilium citandi et executandi for all purposes under this agreement, whether in respect of court process, notice, or other documents or communication of whatsoever nature, South Africa and for ECD - via Telesio 25, Milan, 20145, Italy respectively.

Variation

ECD/SDC may, in its sole discretion, change this agreement or any part thereof at any time without notice.

Company Information

This website is owned and operated by SDC. Owners and Directors information on request at: [sdconline@eucollegeofdesign.com](mailto:sdconline@eucollegeofdesign.com)

### PART D - PRIVACY POLICY

By using this website you accept the terms of this privacy statement and the terms and conditions on this website. 

Our Commitment to Privacy

This privacy statement explains how we collect information from you via the website or in any manner expressly described in the privacy statement and how this information is then used. When you provide us with your personal data in the manner described, you consent to the processing of all such personal data as set out in the privacy statement. Please read this privacy statement carefully and revisit this page from time to time to review any changes that we may have made. If you have any questions or comments about how we handle your personal information, please email: [sdconline@eucollegeofdesign.com](mailto:sdconline@eucollegeofdesign.com)

You may also use these contacts to tell us about any concerns you may have about our privacy statement. 

Giving Information for Other People 

When you provide us with information about another person, the other person must have agreed to let: 

  * us process all their personal data contained in the information provided; and
  * you receive any data protection notices for them.   

When you send information for someone else, you are confirming that you have told them : 

  * which data they must give;
  * which information is voluntary; and 
  * how they can access and, if necessary, correct the data we hold about them.   

The Information we Collect During Registration or Enrolment 

When you register with us, you (or the person registering for you) must tell us: 

  * your full name
  * email address 
  * your date of birth   

Following registration via the Website, we, or our Agents (where you have been introduced to the Website via an Agent or Reseller), may request additional personal data from you in order to further support your learning. You do not have to provide this information, but if you do not, you may not get the most out of your learning. 

Other Information we Collect 

You may also provide personal data through: 

  * calls to our helplines;
  * letters and e-mails; 
  * customer feedback forms.   

We may record calls to helplines for quality and training purposes only. We will store calls for about three months and we will keep them confidential. In general, if you contact us, we may keep a record of your query or complaint for a reasonable time in case you contact us again. 

How we Use the Information we Collect 

We use your personal information: 

  * to answer your queries or complaints;
  * to deliver our online services, for example any Courses that you have access to 
  * to provide Course Materials; 
  * to carry out administration; 
  * to seek your opinion of the Course and Website 
  * for general statistics and research; 
  * for obtaining any relevant professional advice; 
  * as may be required by law or in connection with legal proceedings (including where we intend to take legal proceedings), or as may be necessary to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights.   

Third Parties and Sponsors 

To achieve the purposes set out in this privacy statement we may need to give your information to our service providers, Agents and Resellers. Following registration and/or enrolment via the website, we and our Agent or Resellers, if you registered via one of our Agents or Resellers, will have access to your name and contact details to help us deliver our services to you. 

Keeping you Informed 

We, and our Agents or Resellers, will use your information to send you regular updates about: 

  * our services and materials;
  * additions to the Website; and 
  * specific activities such as customer feedback surveys and competitions.   

If you wish to receive information about SDC developments and offers by telephone, email and/or SMS, please invite us to contact you by ticking the appropriate boxes. If at any time, you change your mind about receiving updates, you can contact us and we will alter your stated preferences accordingly. 

We will never use your personal data for marketing purposes or to target you for customer feedback purposes without your express consent.

Requests for Information 

If you have not registered on the Website but are simply making an enquiry or request for information, we will use your personal information to reply to your enquiry or request. We will not use this information for marketing purposes without your permission or unless you invite us to do so. 

Protecting your Personal Information 

SDC is required to take appropriate technical measures to protect your personal information including making a regular backup of our system and data. We have security measures in place to make sure any personal information we collect is secure. Your account is password protected and all information including your password is on a secure server, which only a limited number of employees and sub-contractors can access. All parties with access to your information are subject to confidentiality obligations. If you think someone else knows your password, or is using it, tell us immediately and change your password. You can change your password on the Website. 

Even though we take appropriate technical steps to protect your security, you should remember that data transmission over the internet cannot always be guaranteed as 100% secure so you use the website at your own risk. 

Cookies 

Cookies are small text files which are sent to your browser by a web server and stored on your personal computer's hard disk. We use cookies on our site to: 

  * cut down the number of times you have to type in data;
  * record the success of advertising, to target advertising and to track visitor usage; and 
  * track responses to regular customer surveys and to make sure you don't see the same survey more than once.   

The cookies used on the website do not collect your personal information. 

You can disable cookies. If you want to know how to remove cookies from your browser, go to the 'All About Cookies' website. 

Transparent .gif Files 

Some of our webpages may contain invisible electronic tags that allow us to count users that have visited certain pages. These files are only used to identify which advertisements bring customers to our website and you cannot be identified by them. They are not issued by us but by the relevant advertising provider. You can find out more about cookie type devices issued by third party advertisers by clicking through to the website operated by the relevant advertiser. 

In any event, you can find out more information about electronic tags, if you go to the 'All About Cookies' website. 

Your Rights 

You have the right to ask for a copy of all the information we hold about you (we will charge you a small fee for this) and to correct any inaccuracies. To obtain a copy of this information, please contact us. You can amend your details on the website at any time on your ‘My SDC’ home page. 

Links 

Our website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of other sites and we advise you to read the privacy statement of every website that collects personal information from you.

### PART E - COPYRIGHT NOTICE

Your use of the content provided on this Website is subject to the terms of this Copyright Statement. 

Ownership 

This website is owned by SDC 

The copyright in the content provided on this Website including all of the graphics, code, text products, software, audio, music and design is owned by SDC except where otherwise indicated. © SDC Online 2014. All rights reserved. 

Copyright in any Course Materials including course notes, materials and teaching aids which will be made available to you if you enrol on a Course with SDC Online via this Website belongs to the relevant SDC Online provider or its licensors. The use of all Course Materials is subject to Part C of the Terms of Use. 

The "SDC" and "SDC Online" marks and the "styledesigncollege.com domain name are the property of SDC. You agree not to copy, reproduce, upload, post, display or use in any way the SDC Online Marks without the prior written permission of SDC. 

Use of the Website 

You are granted a limited personal non-exclusive licence to use the Course Materials for the maximum duration of each course. As such, you may print course material for your personal use. Save as expressly set out in this Copyright Notice, you may not modify, copy, reproduce, re-publish, upload, post, transmit or distribute in any way any of the Course Materials. Any use of the Course Materials not expressly permitted in this Copyright Notice is strictly prohibited and will constitute an infringement of the copyright and other intellectual property rights of SDC, or in the case of material licensed to SDC, the owner of such materials. 

You agree not to delete, change or modify in any way this Copyright Notice on this Website.
